[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the director of Cape Fear?", "correct_answer": "Martin Scorsese", "incorrect_answers": ["Wesley Stricle", "Wes Craven", "Ron Howard"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "After Michael finds out what kind of guy Stephanie wants in the movie Grease 2, he saves up money to buy something to impress her by doing which of the following?", "correct_answer": "writing papers for members of the boys group", "incorrect_answers": ["selling drugs", "working at the local malt shop", "tutoring people in English"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1935, a full length cartoon version of Gullivers Travels was made. What was unusual about it?", "correct_answer": "It told the story from a Communist point of view.", "incorrect_answers": ["It uses much of the exact dialog from Swifts novel.", "It is told as a flashback.", "It combines animation and human actors."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these handsome African American actors stars in the 2003 The Fighting Temptations movie?", "correct_answer": "Cuba Gooding, Jr.", "incorrect_answers": ["Jamie Foxx", "Will Smith", "Denzel Washington"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is a 1993 black and white movie that won the Best Picture Award?", "correct_answer": "Schindlers List", "incorrect_answers": ["Citizen Kane", "Black and White in Color", "The Manchurian Candidate"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This French car manufacturer also produces vans, buses, tractors, and trucks. The brand was established in 1899.", "correct_answer": "None of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Peugeot", "Citroen", "Bugatti"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "His wife was Ruby Dee and together they build a career in movie and television and were both very active in the Civil Rights movement. He starred as the operator of the baitshop in Grumpy Old Men.", "correct_answer": "Ossie Davis", "incorrect_answers": ["Ozzie Davis", "Sammy Davis", "Sid Davis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Sam Witwickys best friend in the movie Transformers?", "correct_answer": "Myles", "incorrect_answers": ["Mike", "Mark", "Mulder"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This was the leader of the group that searched Loch Ness in the early 1970s and claimed to have made underwater photographs of the monster.", "correct_answer": "Dr. Robert Rines", "incorrect_answers": ["MR Trules", "Sir Peter Scott", "Professor Jankins"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The movie The Blair Witch Project is based on a real legend.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the color of the little girls coat that catches the eye of Oskar Schindler in Steven Spielbergs 1993 movie Schindlers List?", "correct_answer": "Red", "incorrect_answers": ["Green", "White", "Black and white"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Scientists are using this animal to try and find a vaccine for leprosy.", "correct_answer": "Armadillos", "incorrect_answers": ["Poison dart frogs", "Sea Urchins", "Bats"]}]